JUAN JOSE VANEGAS MAYA

CONTACT INFO

647-568-1890

Juanjovanegas21@gmail.com

210 Victoria St, Toronto

www.linkedin.com/in/juanjose-vanegas-maya/

github.com/jvane1

EDUCATION

Advanced Diploma in Electronics Engineering Technology

Seneca College, Toronto, ON September 2017– December 2019

Scholarships / Leadership Awards:

Seneca Student Federation International Student Award and Campus Living Centre Academic.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Communication
Building Relationships
Critical Thinking
Innovation
Perseverance

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office Figma
CSS HTML
Python ReactJS

GitHub C

Salesforce

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Result-driven and motivated software engineering enthusiast with demonstrated experience in both business and software development. Quick learner and easy adopter to new technologies and existing projects. Proven record of collaborating in real-world web applications accountable for \$1.3M in annual revenue.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Electronics Sales Account Manager

Bittele Electronics Inc, Jan 2020 - Present

- Technical point of contact for sales prospects and existing clients. Currently
 managing over 540 client accounts. Communicating with 10-20 client
 accounts daily with the help of CRM and ERP systems.
- As an experienced sales account manager, I have closed 333 sales exceeding the target number of sales to-date for financial year by 35%.
- In charge of supervising and upkeeping with the online ordering system which is accountable for 1.3M in annual sales revenue.
- As an effective supervisor, I demonstrated success by reaching 90.3% of the annual sales value target within the first 9 months of the financial year.
- Responsible for quickly and iteratively create user flows, wireframes, prototypes, and high-fidelity mock-ups for internal sales software-related projects.
- Work in collaboration with the software development team and sales manager to enhance UI and UX, and re-architecting and maintaining the online ordering system using tools like Figma.

Senior Research Assistant

Seneca College, July 2019 - October 2020

- Work closely with research project manager and professors in the planning, designing, and prototyping of two research projects:
- ✓ Universal retrofit system for autonomous control of robotic wet/dry cleaners for client Cyberworks Robotics Inc. (September 2019 October 2020).
- ✓ Eco-Friendly, Automatic Equine Water Trough System for Lenka Equestrian Centre. (July 2019 December 2019).
- Demonstrated professionalism and work ethic by delivering well-organized and on-time documentation (Oct 2020 and Dec 2019 respectively).

LANGUAGES & OTHER INTERESTS

- Fluent in English and Spanish.
- Co-Founder and Co-President of the company Uniqoffee Ltd. -Arkaika Coffee in 2018. ArkaikaCoffee.com / @arkaikacoffee!
- Co-founder of the clothing brand Lima Rosa, Colombia, 2019.
 @LimaRosatiendaderopa
- Software development enthusiast: Currently working in a personal portfolio using technologies like Figma, GitHub, HTML, CSS, ReactJS and Firebase.
- Direct contributor to the development of Professor Benjamin Shefler's new course MCO556 – ARM® Microcontroller for Real-time Embedded Applications at Seneca College (2020).